<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Main Story]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Main Story</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 22:35:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 22:35:32 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator/><item><title><![CDATA[Scene 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>FarnenJesnen, what ails you?JesnenFather, I am not exactly sure how to put this specific feeling into words.FarnenHow many words have I taught you? How many words has the Sanctum taught you? You are disrespecting the Sanctum if you cannot learn through this.JesnenI will try. I did not intend to disrespect you or the Sanctum. 'Scopaesthesia' seems to be a word in the proper direction but it is not right.FarnenSon, who is watching you? Is someone causing your ailment.JesnenNo, it feels like I am being watched but it is not of this universe.JesnenI'm not certain.FarnenSon, we know everything of this universe. If someone or something was watching you, the Sanctum would be the first to know. This is all in your head. Visiting other universes is strictly prohibited. We know none of the information that sits within them.FarnenVisit the Sanctum Crest. I'm reporting this and requesting a memory countermand for you.JesnenOkay Father, I will go now.<br><br><br>Sanctum CrestJesnen, we have read the report from your father, why did you not come sooner?JesnenI could not think of the word to describe what I was feeling and I had not thought a memory countermand was necessary yet.Sanctum CrestMemory countermands are conducted for duplicate or unnecessary knowledge for all those in the Sanctum, they give clearer pathways to sharing all knowledge. Given that is everything is already known we are working to retire this procedure. We are not going through with a memory countermand for you.JesnenThan what shall I do with this feeling.Sanctum CrestWe are going to send you to the universe from where your feeling is coming from, Jesnen. We are ready to move past the Sanctum. You are the first to come with this feeling, if there are others than they will be sent as well. It seems your feeling might be a calling card to expand our knowledge outside of the Sanctum.<br><br><br>Sam So what book are you going to pick?Ninety I don't know.NinetySummer reading is stupid. If we read in the Summer than we shouldn't have to read during the semester.SamThat makes no sense.NinetyScratch that, it should be that you get to swap your reading so if you don't read in the Summer than you don't have to read in the Fall.SamThat also makes no sense.NinetyDo you ever agree with me?Sam We both liked that movie we went to last week.Sam...Actually that's not true, I agreed with you so that we could go to the arcade later in thatNinety That's messed up.Sam I think I'm going to pick this one. 'The Alchemist.' I think Jasmine picked this one tooNinetyWow, picking the shortest book and copying Jasmine.SamI'll have something to talk with her about.Ninety Yeah, you can talk about all]]></description><link>phaymo.github.io/manuscript.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">phaymo.github.io/manuscript.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 22:35:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>